havasmedia.com 2017-06-19

# Privacy Policy | Havas Media

##  19 June 2017

## PRIVACY AND PERSONAL DATA  

We inform you that the website [www.havasmedia.com](http://www.havasmedia.com/) (the “Website”) is operated by Havas Media Group Spain, S.A.U.. (hereinafter, “HMGS”, “we”, “us” or “our”), with Tax I.D. Code (“C.I.F.”) A–78.809.662, entered at the Commercial Registry of Barcelona on volume 37.673, folio 220, page B-221.687, and registered office at Barcelona, Avda Diagonal, 575, Edificio L’Illa. HMGS is adhered to Confianza On-line. You may obtain further information on HMGS in the section “Who we are” and “What we do” of the Website or by sending an e-mail to the following e-mail address [privacy.hvm@havasmedia.com](mailto:privacy.hvm@havasmedia.com) “You” and “Your” means you as the user of our Website.

This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") is intended to inform You how we gather, define, and use Your Information (as defined below). This Privacy Policy, and our separate Terms of Use and our Cookies Policy, make up our Website “Terms and Conditions”.

Access to and use of the Website by You implies Your full acceptance of the Website Terms and Conditions. In this regard, if You access and use the Website You agree to comply with the provisions indicated in the mentioned legal documents. The provision of the Website service is limited to the period during which You are connected to the Website or to any of the services provided via same. Therefore, You must read this Privacy Policy carefully each time You intend to use the Website, since it may undergo changes.  
All Your personal Information shall be held and used in accordance with the Personal Data Protection Law (the "Legislation"). If You want to know what information we collect and hold about You, please write to us at [privacy.hvm@havasmedia.com](mailto:privacy.hvm@havasmedia.com).

HMGS is the data controller of the personal data that we will collect from You.  

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT  

When You visit our Website You may provide us with personal data in a number of ways, among other:  

  1. by completing a data collection form on our Website or
  2. by corresponding with us by email, in which case we may retain the content of Your email messages together with Your email address and our responses.  

Furthermore, by accessing the Website we may also collect information about Your computer, including where available Your IP address, operating system and browser type of Your computer, for system administration.

## HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US?  

In compliance with the legislation, we inform You that the personal data collected through Your access to the Website or through any data collection forms of the Website will be included in a personal data filing system of which HMGS is the data controller.

We use Your information with the purposes to (i) manage Your navigation through the Website and (ii) for the purposes indicated in each data collection forms. Please note that when You click the button “submit” included in each data collection form, You declare that the information and personal data provided are accurate and updated.  

With Your consent, we may disclose Your personal information to the entities of the group of companies to which HMGS belongs, the group includes, but is not limited, the following companies: ARCHIBALD INGALL STRETTON, S.L.; ARENA MEDIA COMMUNICATIONS ESPAÑA, S.A.U.; ARENA COMMUNICATIONS NETWORK, S.L.; ARTEMIS ALLIANCE, S.L.U.; ELISA INTERACTIVE, S.L.U.; HAVAS, S.A.; HAVAS MANAGEMENT ESPAÑA, S.L.U.; HAVAS MEDIA, S.L.U.; HAVAS MEDIA ALLIANCE, S.L.U.; HAVAS MEDIA ALLIANCE WW, S.L.U. ;HAVAS MEDIA CONSULTING, S.L.U.; HAVAS SPORTS, S.A.U.; IGLUE MEDIA, S.L.U.; INNOVATION RESEARCH MANAGEMENT LAB, S.L.U.; FORWARD HOLDING SPAIN, S.L.U.; FORWARD MEDIA COMMUNICATION; MEDIA ADVISORS, S.A.U.; MEDIA CONTACTS, S.A.U.; MEDIA CONTACTS MOBILE, S.L.U.; HAVAS MEDIA  GROUP SPAIN, S.A.U; MEDIA PLANNING LEVANTE, S.L.U.; METRICS IN MARKETING, S.A.U.; PROXIMIA BALEARS, S.L.; PROXIMIA HAVAS, S.L.U.; RESEARCH AND DEVELOPPEMENT CONSULTING LAB; RESEARCH AND DEVELOPPEMENT MARKETING LAB, S.L.U. UNCOMMON HOLDING SPAIN, S.A.U.

In limited circumstances we may pass Your Information to other third party organisations if we are under a duty to disclose or share Your Information to comply with any legal obligation or in order to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements or protect the rights, property, or safety of our clients, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.  

## COMMERCIAL COMMUNICATIONS  

We inform You that we can collect Your consent with the purposes to send You commercial communications through each data collection form. Where You have expressly consented, by filling in the opt-in box that may appear in the data collection form when browsing our Website we may contact You by email, post, sms, or through any other equivalent electronic communication mean, with information about our products or services that we feel may be of interest to You. You can let us know at any time if You no longer wish to receive these communications by contacting [privacy.hvm@havasmedia.com](mailto:privacy.hvm@havasmedia.com).  

## COOKIES

Similar to other commercial websites, our Website uses a technology called "cookies" and web server logs to collect information about how our Website is used. For details about how we use cookies, please see our Cookies Policy.  

## YOUR CONSENT  

By using our Website You consent to our collection and use of certain data as described in this Privacy Policy and our Cookie Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Website to keep You aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.  

We also inform You that You may revoke the consent given for the processing of Your data, whenever this is legally appropriate, by sending a notice to HMGS as provided below.

## HOW CAN YOU ACCESS YOUR INFORMATION  

We inform You that You may exercise at any time Your rights of access, rectification, cancellation and objection to the processing of Your personal data by sending a written notice, attaching a photocopy of a document evidencing Your identity, to the following address: Eloy Gonzalo 10, Madrid 28010 or [privacy.hvm@havasmedia.com](mailto:privacy.hvm@havasmedia.com). Such notice shall be sent for the attention of the L.O.P.D. Consultation Office (Oficina de Consulta L.O.P.D.).

## WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA  

Personal data and information we collect from You may be transferred to and stored at a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). All the previous will be in accordance with Legislation. Furthermore, we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your Information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Cookies Policy.  

## SECURITY

We have implemented and we maintain the highest standards of security required by the Legislation to protect Your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. However the transmission of information via Internet is not completely secure. So, whilst we will do our best to protect Your Information, we cannot ensure the security of Your data during transit to our Website. Any information You submit is sent at Your own risk. Once we have received Your Information we will use strict procedures and security features to prevent unauthorised access.  

## THIRD PARTY SITES  

Our Website browser and application may contain links to sites controlled by third parties. Please remember that when You use a link to go from our Website to another website, our Privacy Policy and Cookies Policy is no longer in effect. This Privacy Policy does not reflect the privacy practices of those third party sites. Please bear in mind that we are not responsible for the privacy and data processing of other websites. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which are linked to ours, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. We recommend that You read the privacy and data processing policies of other websites that You may visit using the link in our Website or in any other manner. For more information please see our Terms of Use.
